The college books are open wide With my whole
world right by my side A quiet laugh, a knowing
look A chapter from a favorite book The future's
just a distant shore I couldn't ask for anything
more Than this small room, this gentle space A
perfect time, a perfect place And I've got my
three guys Lighting stars Healing all my
childhood scars A sister's strength, a
sister's grace A best friend's warm and kind
embrace This is the only life I need A perfect,
rare, and precious creed Yeah, I'm nineteen and
invincible
with a love that's unconditional.
Thank you.
We talk for hours on the phone I never feel like
I'm alone You get the jokes inside my head On
every single word unsaid We're just a team of
misfit souls Making each other brave and whole
No need to search, no need to roam Cause with the
three of you I'm home
Yeah, the world is out there, big and wide But
I've got nothing left to hide With my team right
here, my crew, my friends The story never has to
end We're gonna chase the summer sun Our real
adventure's just begun Got a full tank and a
radio And everywhere is ours to go And I feel the
rhythm, I feel the beat of my own We're coming
back to the kids we knew in shades of brilliant
white and blue. This is the sound of being free.
This is the sound of being me.
And I feel the rhythm, I feel the beat Of my own
heart on a crowded street We're coming back to
the kids we knew In shades of brilliant white and
blue This is the sound of being free
This is the sound of me and me